Jascha Heifetz Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1911-1974 (Box 1-247)
  - Music by Other Composers (Box-folder 15/2-11, Box 16-247)
    - Composers
      - Koutzen, Boris
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 2], Score (Box-folder 112/4)
      - Kreisler, Fritz
        - Allegretto [in the style of Boccherini], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/5)
        - Andante [in the style of Martini], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/6)
        - Aubade provençale [in the style of Couperin], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/7)
        - Caprice viennois, Piano-violin score and part; Piano-violin score only (Box-folder 112/8)
        - Chanson Louis XII [in the style of Couperin], Piano-violin score only (Box-folder 112/9)
        - La chasse [in the style of Cartier], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/10)
        - Farewell to Cucullian (Londonderry air), Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/11)
        - La Gitania, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/12)
        - Grave [in the style of Friedemann Bach], Piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 112/13)
        - Liebesfreud, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 112/14)
        - Liebesleid, Piano-violin score and part; Piano-violin score only (Box-folder 113/1)
        - Menuett [in the style of Porpora], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 113/2)
        - Polichinelle, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 113/3)
        - Praeludium und Allegro [in the style of Pugnani], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 113/4)
        - La Précieuse [in the style of Couperin], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 113/5)
        - [Quartet, strings, A minor], Parts (Box-folder 113/6)
        - [Quartet, strings, A minor], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - Recitativo and scherzo, Violin score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 113/7)
        - Romanze, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 113/8)
        - Rondino (on a theme by Beethoven), Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 113/9)
        - Schön Rosmarin, Piano-violin score and part (3) (Box-folder 113/10)
        - Siciliano & Allegro [in the style of Francoeur], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 113/11)
        - Tambourin chinois, Piano-violin score and part; 2 copies (Box-folder 113/12)
        - Favorite encore folio, Piano-violin score and part; Edited by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 114/1)
      - Kreutzer, Rodolphe
        - Etudes, Violin score (Box-folder 114/2)
        - Caprice-humoresque, Piano-violin score only (Box-folder 114/3)
        - Etude-caprice, Violin part only (Box-folder 114/4)
      - Kroll, Louis
        - Banjo and fiddle, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 114/5)
        - Perpetual motion, Holograph [?] piano-violin score (Box-folder 114/6)
      - Kubik, Gail
        - [Concerto, violin, D major], Ozalid of ms. orchestral score (Box-folder 244/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, D major], Ozalid of violin part (Box-folder 244/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, D major; arr.], Ozalid of ms. piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 244/2)
        - [Sonatina, violin, piano], Ozalid of ms. piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 244/3)
      - Labunski, Wiktor
        - Mazurek, Holograph [?] piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 114/7)
      - Lalo, Edouard
        - [Syphonie espagnole, violin, orchestra], Orchestral score (Box-folder 114/8)
        - [Syphonie espagnole, violin, orchestra], Parts (Box-folder 114/9-10, Box-folder 115/1)
        - [Symphonie espagnole, violin, orchestra; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 115/2-3)
      - Langendoen, J.
        - Fantasia, Violin score (Box-folder 115/4)
      - Langstroth, Ivan
        - 9 variations on an etude by F. Fiorillo, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 115/5)
      - Lauricella, Remo
        - African interlude, Photostat of holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 115/6)
        - African interlude, Holograph violin part (Box-folder 115/6)
        - African interlude, Copyist's ms. of piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 115/6)
        - African interlude, Printed piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 115/6)
        - Danza siciliana, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 116/1)
        - [Triquetra, violin, orchestra; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 116/2)
        - [Triquetra, violin, orchestra; arr.], Photostat of holograph violin part (Box-folder 116/2)
      - Leclair, Jean Marie
        - [Tambourin; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 116/3)
      - Lecouna, Ernesto
        - Andalucia (suite espagnole), Piano score (Box-folder 116/4)
        - Danzas afro-cubans, Piano score (Box-folder 116/5)
        - One more tomorrow, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 116/6)
      - Léonard, Hubert
        - Variations sur une gavotte de Corelli, Piano-violin score (Box-folder 116/7)
      - Léonard, Hubert; François Servais
        - 2me grand duo de concert sur des thêmes de Beethoven, Photostat and negative photostat of violin and cello parts (Box-folder 116/8)
      - Lewis, Rosemary
        - I'd rather listen to you, Holograph fragment of piano-vocal score (Box-folder 116/9)
        - I'd rather listen to you, Photostat of holograph piano-vocal score (Box-folder 116/9)
        - There's love everywhere, Photostat of holograph piano-vocal score (Box-folder 116/10)
        - Too soon, Photostat of holograph piano-vocal score (Box-folder 116/11)
      - Leoncavallo, Ruggero
        - [Pagliacci; arr.], Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 116/12)
      - Liadov, Anatoli
        - Compositions pour piano, Piano score (Box-folder 116/13)
        - [Works, piano. Selections], Piano score (Box-folder 117/1)
      - Liapunov, Sergei
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 61], Ms. violin part (Box-folder 117/2)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 61; arr.], Photostat of holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 117/3)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 61; arr.], Printed piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 117/4)
      - Limonick, Maurice
        - Summer serenade, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 117/5)
      - Liszt, Franz
        - [Ce qu'on entend sur la montagne, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Concerto, piano, no. 1, E-flat major; arr.], 2 piano, 4 hands score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 117/6)
        - [Eine Faust-Symphonie, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Festklänge, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Héroïde funèbre, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Hungaria, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 211)
        - [Hunneschlacht, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Die Ideale, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Mazeppa, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Orpheus, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Les préludes, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Prometheus, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Tasso, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Valse-Impromptu; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Jenö Hubay (Box-folder 117/7)
      - Locatelli, Pietro
        - Twee sonates voor viool met pianobegeleidung, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 117/8)
        - Sonata de camera, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 118/1)
      - Lockwood, Normand
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 3], Score (Box-folder 118/2)
      - Loeffler, Charles Martin
        - Music for four stringed instruments, String quartet parts (Box-folder 118/3)
      - Loeillet, Jean Baptiste
        - [Gigue; arr.], Piano score (Box-folder 118/4)
      - Loewe, Carl
        - Canzonetta, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 118/5)
      - Löhr, Herman
        - Where my caravan has rested, Piano-vocal score, violin and cello parts (Box-folder 118/6)
        - [Where my caravan has rested; arr.], Ms. 4-stave score (Box-folder 244/4)
      - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 26; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 118/7)
      - MacDowell, Edward
        - Woodland sketches, Piano score (Box-folder 118/8)
      - McEwen, John
        - [Quartet, strings], Parts (Box-folder 118/9)
      - Malipiero, Gian Francesco
        - Stornelli e ballate, String quartet parts (Box-folder 118/10)
      - Mana-Zucca
        - Fisherman's Wharf, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 118/11)
        - [Frolic; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 118/12)
      - Martinů, Bohislav
        - Duo, Parts (Box-folder 118/13)
        - Rhythmische Etüden, Piano-violin score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 118/14)
      - Mason, Daniel Gregory
        - Fanny Blair folk-song fantasy, String quartet score (Box-folder 118/15)
      - Massenet, Jules
        - Élégie, Piano-vocal score and violin and cello parts (Box-folder 119/1)
        - Élégie, Piano-violin score (Box-folder 119/1)
        - Élégie, Cello part (Box-folder 119/1)
        - Méditation, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 119/2)
      - Medtner, Nicolai
        - Quatre contes, Piano score (Box-folder 119/3)
        - [Fairy tale, op. 26, no. 3, F minor], Piano score (Box-folder 119/4)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 1, op. 21, B minor], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 119/5)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 2, op. 44, G major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 119/6)
        - Sonata epica, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 119/7)
      - Mendelssohn, Felix
        - [Concerto, piano, no. 1, op. 25, G minor; arr.], 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 119/8)
        - [Concerto, piano, no. 2, op. 40, D minor; arr.], 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 119/9)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 64, E minor], Orchestral score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 119/10)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 64, E minor], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 64, E minor], Parts (Box-folder 120/1-3)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 64, E minor; arr.], Piano-violin score (3) and part (2); Various editions (Box-folder 120/4)
        - Auf Flügeln des Gesanges, Piano-violin sore and part; Arranged by Joseph Achron (Box-folder 120/5)
        - [Lieder ohne Worte. Selections; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 121/1)
        - [Lieder ohne Worte, op. 62, no. 1; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 121/2)
        - [Octet, strings, op. 20, E-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 121/3)
        - [Quartets, piano, strings, no. 1-3], Parts (Box-folder 121/4)
        - [Quartets, strings, no. 1-5], Parts (Box-folder 121/5, Box-folder 122/1)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 3, op. 44, no. 1, D major], Parts (Box-folder 122/2)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 4, op. 44, no. 2, E minor], Parts (Box-folder 122/3)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 5, op. 44, no. 3, E-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 122/4)
        - [Quintets, strings, no. 1-2], Parts (Box-folder 122/5)
        - [Dem Sommernachtstraum, op. 61. Selections], Miniature score; Various editions (2) (Box 212)
        - Symphonien A moll. A dur, Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Trios, piano, strings, no. 1-2], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 122/6)
        - Kammermusik, Miniature score (Box 212)
      - Menotti, Gian Carlo
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 123/1)
      - Meyer, B. v. d. Sigtenhorst
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 13], Parts (Box-folder 123/2)
      - Miaskovsky, Nicolai
        - [Sinfonietta, op. 32, no. 2], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Symphony, no. 21, op. 51], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Symphony, no. 22, op. 54], Miniature score (Box 212)
      - Milhaud, Darius
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 1, op. 93; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Second movement only (Box-folder 123/3)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 2, op. 263], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, op. 373; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 123/4)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 1, op. 5], Parts (Box-folder 123/5)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 4, op. 46], Parts (Box-folder 123/6)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 6, op. 77], Parts (Box-folder 123/7)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 8, op. 121], Parts (Box-folder 123/8)
        - Leme, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 123/9)
        - Corvacado, Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 123/10)
        - Sumaré, Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 123/11)
        - [Scaramouche, op. 167b], 2 piano, 4 hands score (2) (Box-folder 123/12)
      - Moeran, Ernest John
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Laid in: letter (Box-folder 123/13)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 123/14)
      - Mohaupt, Richard
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Ozalid of ms. piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 244/5)
      - Mompou, Federico
        - [Canción y Danza, no. 6], Piano score (Box-folder 124/1)
        - Combat del somni, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 124/2)
        - [Scènes d'enfants. Jeunes filles au jardin; arr.], Piano-violin score; Arranged by Joseph Szigeti (Box-folder 124/3)
      - Monsigny, Pierre Alexandre
        - [Rigaudon; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Sam Franko (Box-folder 124/4)
      - Moore, Douglas
        - [Quartet, strings], Score (Box-folder 124/5)
      - Moszkowski, Moritz
        - [Guitarre, op. 45, no. 2; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (2); Arranged by Pablo Sarasate (Box-folder 124/6)
        - [Suite, violins (2), piano, op. 77], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 124/7)
      - Mouret, Jean-Joseph
        - [Menuet, G minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 124/8)
        - [Sararbande; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 124/9)
      - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, K. 216, G major], Photostat of holograph orchestral score (Box-folder 124/10)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, K. 216, G major], Negative photostat of holograph orchestral score (Box-folder 124/11)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, K. 216, G major], Printed orchestral score (Box-folder 125/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, K. 216, G major], Parts (Box-folder 125/2)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, K. 216, G major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 125/3)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 4, K. 218, D major], Orchestral score (Box-folder 125/4)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 4, K. 218, D major], Parts (Box-folder 125/5, Box-folder 126/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 4, K. 218, D major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 126/2)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 5, K. 219, A major], Orchestral score (Box-folder 126/3)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 5, K. 219, A major], Parts (Box-folder 126/4-5)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 5, K. 219, A major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 127/1)
        - Konzert Nr. 6 Es dur, Orchestral score (Box-folder 127/2)
        - Konzert Nr. 6 Es dur, Parts (Box-folder 127/3-4)
        - [Concerto, violin, Anhang C. 14.04, E-flat major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 128/1)
        - [Duets, violin, viola], Parts (Box-folder 128/2)
        - Divertimente, Full score (Box-folder 128/3)
        - Sextett, Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Divertimento, strings, K. 320b, D major. Menuet; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 128/4)
        - [Divertimento, violin, viola, cello, K. 563, E-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 128/5)
        - [Eine Kleine Nachtmusik, K. 525, G major], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Musikalischer Spass, string quartet, horns (2), K. 522], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Musikalischer Spass, string quartet, horns (2), K. 522], Parts (Box-folder 128/6)
        - [Overtures. Selections; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 128/7)
        - [Quartets, piano, strings], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 128/8)
        - [Quartet, strings, K. 421, D minor, Menuetto; arr.], Parts (Box-folder 128/9)
        - [Quartet, strings, K. 499, D major], Parts; First edition (1786) (Box-folder 128/10)
        - Trois [i.e. six] quators [1802], Parts (Box-folder 129/1)
        - [Quartets, strings. Selections], Parts; band I (Box-folder 129/2-3)
        - [Quartets, strings. Selections], Parts; band II (Box-folder 129/4)
        - [Quintet, strings, K. 614, E-flat major], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Quintets, strings. Selections], Parts (Box-folder 130/1-2)
        - [Quintets, strings. Selections], Parts; With other Mozart works arr. for string quintet (Box-folder 130/3)
        - [Quintets, strings. Selections], Violin I part only (Box-folder 130/4)
        - [Serenade, K. 248b, D major], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - Rondo [from "Haffner" serenade], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 130/5)
        - XII quators, Parts; 1802 edition (Box-folder 130/6)
        - [Sonatas, violin, piano], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 131/1)
        - [Sonatas, violin, piano], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 132/1)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 8, K. 296, C major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 132/2)
        - Krebsgang, Parts (Box-folder 132/3)
        - Table music, Parts; With music by Mestrino (Box-folder 132/4)
        - [Sinfonia concertante, violin ,viola, orchestra, K. 320d, E-flat major; arr.], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 133/1)
        - [Symphony, no. 35, K. 385, D major], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Symphony, no. 38, K. 504, D major], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Symphony, no. 39, K. 543, E-flat major], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Symphony, no. 40, K. 550, G minor], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Symphony, no. 41, K. 551, C major], Miniature score; Various editions (2) (Box 212)
        - [Symphonies. Selections], Orchestral score (Box-folder 133/2)
        - [Symphonies. Selections; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score; Folders: 133/3 Volume 1 133/4 Volume 2 (Box-folder 133/3-4)
        - [Trios, piano, strings], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 133/5)
        - [Works, instrumental. Selections], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - Master series for the young, Piano score (Box-folder 134/1)
      - Nardini, Pietro
        - [Concerto, violin, E minor], Parts (Box-folder 134/2)
        - [Concerto, violin, E minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 134/3)
        - [Sonata, violin, continuo, D major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 134/4)
      - Nero, Paul
        - The fiddle that went west, Piano-violin score and part; Laid in: letter (Box-folder 134/5)
        - Suite for hot fiddle, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 134/6)
      - Netto, Barozzo
        - Minha terra, Piano score (Box-folder 134/7)
      - Nielsen, Carl
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 33], Orchestral score (Box-folder 134/8)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 33; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 134/9)
      - Nin, Joaquin
        - Cantilena asturiana, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 134/10)
      - Nováček, Ottokar
        - Perpetuum mobile, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 134/11)
      - Oransky, Victor
        - Kindelieder, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 134/12)
      - Orgad, Ben-Zion
        - Ballada, Violin score (Box-folder 134/13)
      - Paganini, Nicoló
        - Caprices, Violin score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 134/14)
        - [Caprice, no. 8, B-flat major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2); Arranged by Fritz Kreisler; Arranged by Albert Spalding (Box-folder 135/1)
        - [Caprice, no. 9, E major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Albert Spalding (Box-folder 135/2)
        - [Caprice, no. 20, B minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 135/3)
        - [Caprice, no. 24, A minor; arr.], Piano violin score and part; Various editions (3); Arranged by Leopold Auer; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler; Arranged by Albert Spalding (Box-folder 135/4)
        - [Caprice, no. 24, A minor; arr.], String orchestra score and parts (Box-folder 135/5)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 1, D major; arr.], Orchestral score; Arranged by August Wilhelmj (Box-folder 135/6)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 1, D major; arr.], Parts (Box-folder 135/7-8)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 1, D major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by August Wilhelmj (Box-folder 135/9)
        - Cadenza by Erick Friedman, Photostat of holograph (Box-folder 135/10)
        - Introduction and variations sur la thème "Nel cor più non mi sento", Violin score (Box-folder 136/1)
        - [Introduction Thema und Variationen; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by August Wilhelmj (Box-folder 136/2)
        - [Non più mesto; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 136/3)
        - I palpiti, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 136/4)
        - Serenata concertata, Violin and guitar part (Box-folder 136/5)
        - [La streghe; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 136/6)
        - Variations on "God save the king", Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 136/7)
        - [Works, violin] (Box-folder 136/8)
      - Pierné, Gabriel
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, op. 36, D minor], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 137/1)
      - Pizzetti, Ildebrando
        - [Quartet, strings], Parts (Box-folder 137/2)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, A major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 137/3)
      - Poidras, Henri
        - Etudes-Caprices, Violin score (Box-folder 137/4)
      - Poldowski
        - Tango, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 137/5)
      - Popper, David
        - [Spinnlied, op. 51, no.1; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 137/6)
      - Porter, Cole
        - Begin the beguine, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 137/7)
        - [Begin the beguine; arr.], Piano score (Box-folder 137/8)
        - [Begin the beguine; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 137/9)
        - Night and day, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 137/10)
        - Night and day, Piano score (Box-folder 137/11)
      - Porter, Quincy
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 6], Score (Box-folder 137/12)
      - Poulenc, Francis
        - [Bagatelle, no. 1, D minor], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 138/1)
        - Pastourelle, Piano score (Box-folder 138/2)
        - Promenades, Piano score (Box-folder 138/3)
      - Press, Jacques
        - Hásseneh, Orchestral score (Box-folder 138/4)
      - Prokofiev, Sergei
        - [Alexander Nevsky. op. 78], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Chout, op. 21bis. Selections], Miniature score (Box 212)
        - Cinderella suite no. 1, Miniature score (Box 212)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 1, op. 19, D major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 138/5)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 2, op. 63, G minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 138/6)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 2, op. 63, G minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 138/7)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 2, op. 63, G minor], Ozalid of orchestral score (Box-folder 244/6)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 2, op. 63, G minor], Parts (Box-folder 138/8, Box-folder 140/1-3)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 2, op. 63, G minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 140/4)
        - Five melodies, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 140/5)
        - [Peter and the wolf, op. 67.], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - Suite no. 1, Miniature score (Box 213)
        - Suite no. 2, Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Sonata, violin, op. 115, D major], Violin score (Box-folder 140/6)